You cut yourself? Where?
（子供のペコ）
切ったあ？ どこ？
My knee.
（子供のスマイル）
膝ん所　血が出てる
It's bleeding.
けっ そんなん
ツバ付けときゃ治んよ
Eh, a little spit's enough to fix that.
Okay.
Huh? Say what?
えっ 何？
ごめん　聞こえない
Sorry, I can't hear you.
（風の音）
（子供のペコ）…の味が
...tastes like...
Taste? Like iron?
鉄の？ 味が？
（リポーター）日本の方ですか？
Are you Japanese?
Yes, sir. I'm Japanese, sir.
（江上(えがみ)）そうっす　日本人っす
（リポーター）何しに海外へ？
Why did you go abroad?
I went to a wedding with some friends.
友達と にぎやかに
結婚式に行ってきたんす
（江上の声）
当てのない自分探しの旅でした～
I was on an aimless journey to find myself.
あちこち放浪したけど—
I wandered far and wide but couldn't find any place where I belonged.
どこにも 合う水は
見つけられませんでしたとさ
アハハハ そうっすよね
Yeah, you're right.
（リポーター）
ありがとうございました
Thank you.
Where will I see this on TV?
これ 何チャンすか？
（リポーター）
金曜日の６時半だから見てみて
It'll air on Friday at 6:30, so tune in then!
Gotcha. I'll check it out.
了解っす！ 確認します！
They won't use that footage.
（江上の声）使われねえよな
そういや今日だ　１年前の今日…
I've just remembered what day it is.
It was one year ago today.
あれから あちこち行ったよな
I've been all over the place since then.
Interhigh
Kanagawa Preliminaries
Table Tennis
Akikusa Gymnasium
Men's Singles, Men's Team
Women's Singles, Women's Team
Maybe I'll check out some table tennis.
行ってみっか　卓球
Sorry I lost after you came all the way here, Coach.
It's fine... Upsets like this make the sport interesting.
Yeah. That bowl-headed kid is the real deal,
and I don't say that just because I lost.
I know.
（木村(きむら)）はっ
Heh, guess I don't have time to sit and mope.
Huh?
Crap! He saw me.
（木村）ヤッベー
見つかっちったよ おい
（小枝）
頭 出しすぎなんだよ バカ
You stuck your head out too far, moron.
Was Wenge crying?
（部員）泣いてた？ ウェンガ
（部員）泣くか
As if.
I have to go teach my lost ducklings how to fly.
Did you hear?
（選手）聞いたか？ おい
Kong from Tsujidou lost in straight sets!
辻堂(つじどう)のコンが
ストレートで飛ばされたってよ
For real? Who'd he play?
（選手）
マジかよ　相手誰よ？
（選手）片高(かたこう)の星野(ほしの)たらいう
２年坊らしいぜ
A Katase second-year named Hoshino, apparently.
（選手）ウソ　あそこ月本(つきもと)１本で
あとはカスって話じゃん
No way! Everybody says Tsukimoto's the only one there who's got game!
They sold us a false story.
それ ガセらしいぜ
This Hoshino's supposedly a powerhouse,
何でも星野って野郎 鬼強(おにつよ)で—
準決で当たる風間(かざま)と
張るんじゃねえかってコーチがよ
and Coach thinks he might make a
real go at Kazama in the semifinals.
That's amazing. Kaiou's in trouble.
すげえな そりゃ
海王(かいおう) ピンチじゃん
I think their vice captain, Sanada,
is facing Tsukimoto in the third round.
副将の真田(さなだ)が３回戦で
その月本とぶつかるぜ 確か
それ まじいわ
Not good!
海王のナンバーツーが
予選の３回戦で消えたら—
It'll be no joke if Kaiou's No. 2
gets eliminated in the third round.
シャレにならん
But hey, it'd teach them a good lesson. They're way too full of themselves.
（選手）しかし まあ—
連中 今まで
でけえ顔して のしてたから—
いい薬だな ヘヘッ
Either way, it'll happen on a
whole different planet from ours.
ともあれ俺らとは別次元の話だよ
True, that!
（選手）言えた それ
エッヘヘヘ…
Wild lilies!
（子供のドラゴン）野ゆりだ！
You'll get pollen on yourself.
（のりお）花粉が付くよ
野ゆりの花粉は油っぽいから
なかなか落ちないぞ
Their pollen is greasy, so it's hard to wash off.
でも 父さん大好きな花だ
Your dad still loves them, though!
Birds sure have it good.
（のりお）鳥はいいなあ
It's so easy for them to get all this way up!
こーんな高い所まで すいすいだ
下界で何が起ころうと関係なし
It doesn't matter to them what happens down on the ground.
飛行機のない時代から—
You figure they've watched our ugly wars and stuff since before there were airplanes?
下界の醜い戦なんかを
眺めていたのかな
Dad, watch out.
（子供のドラゴン）
父さん 危ないよ
Dad!
父さん！
（ペコ）フウ…
A new age has dawned, and still I can't make a decision
My path is too straight for my taste, but I'll walk it
I can't choose just yet
I have to think about it
I have no idea what I want to do
I'm going crazy!
Comparing yourself to others just makes you depressed
You're alone in this world
You're always alone here
Still you're gonna do it, right?
Maybe there's nothing that only I can do
But there's no way that I
But there's no way that I won't try to leave my mark
I just want to have my fun, whatever the times
（真田）風間がおらんのう
Kazama's not here.
Ah, no sir.
あ… うっす！
見るに値せん試合っちゅう
ことかいのう
Maybe he thinks this match isn't worth watchin'.
Hey now...
（卓(たく)）おい
監督
１つ聞いてよかですか？
Coach, can I ask you something?
If I win this match, do you figure he'll think a little better of us?
（真田）こん試合ば
もし自分が取りよったら—
やつも ちったあ わしらんごと
見直してくれますかね？
余計なことは考えるな
Don't concern yourself with that.
試合に集中しろ 真田
Focus on your match, Sanada.
Yes, sir!
押忍(おす)！
On court nine, the third-round match between Tsukimoto of Katase High School and Sanada of Kaiou Academy.
９番コート
３回戦 片瀬(かたせ)高校 月本選手
海王学園 真田選手
Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight!
（部員たち）
ファイッ ファイッ ファイッ…
シャーラッ！
Oh yeah!
Is Eyebrows there any good?
（オババ）
強いのかい？ あの眉毛
Sure is, Mom!
（道夫(みちお)）強いよ 母ちゃん
He tends to get overshadowed by Kazama,
風間のおかげで
いまひとつ影が薄いが—
去年のインハイでは
ベスト４
but he's a monster—semifinalist at last year's Interhigh, and he even made it to the round of 16 at nationals.
全日本でもベスト16に入った
モンスターだ
A monster, huh?
（オババ）モンスターねえ…
No problem.
（ペコ）ノープロ ノープロ
スマイルは負けねえさ
Smile won't lose.
Peco! Where the hell have you been?! I looked everywhere for you!
ペコ どこ行ってやがった！
捜したぞ ずいぶん
うんこ
Taking a shit.
下品！
Ew!
Congrats.
（オババ）お疲れさん
（ペコ）なんの
It was nothing.
Blow him away, Smile!
（道夫）吹っ飛ばせ スマイル！
ぶちかましたれー！
Get him good!
So how are you feeling?
（オババ）それで どうなんだい
膝は もちそうかい？
Think your knee will last?
俺たちがついてるぞー！
We're rooting for you!
I'm not blind, kid.
（オババ）
あいにく この目は節穴と違う
Right.
サンキュー オババ　心配ねえわ
Thanks, old lady. No need to worry.
Right.
（道夫）
あっ 見て見て！ こっちだ！
Ah, he looked this way. Over here!
おーい スマイル！ おーい！
Hey, Smile! Hey!
I've been waiting for the day I'd get to play you.
（真田）君と打ち合える日ば
待ち望んじょったけん—
I'm a real happy man today, Tsukimoto.
うれしくて たまらんばい 月本君
海王の真田じゃ
I'm Sanada from Kaiou.
I'm Tsukimoto from Katase High.
（スマイル）
片高の月本です　よろしく
Nice to meet you.
Yeah!
（真田）っしゃー！
（主審）エイトワン　真田選手
Eight-one, Sanada!
Yeah! Yeah!
（歓声）
（真田）っしゃー！ っしゃー！
He's got crazy power!
何ちゅうパワーだ
あれでは
スマイルでも手が出ねえ
Even Smile can't do anything against that!
Oh? Well, that is a problem.
へえ そりゃ困ったね どうも
（スマイル）くっ
（真田）っしゃー！
Yeah!
（主審）アウト！ ナインワン
Out!
Nine-one!
Looks like even the "prince" is done for.
（高村(たかむら)）さすがの王子様も
万事休すかね　ヘヘ
（大田(おおた)）うーん
Coach and Kazama think so much of him that I was pretty scared,
（真田の声）
監督や風間が買いかぶりよるけ
ずいぶん臆しよったが
but in the end, he's...
ふた開けりゃ しょせん—
片高ばい
just a Katase player.
Go get him!
サッ １本！
Go!
（卓の声）マズいな
This is trouble.
Just you watch, Kazama.
（真田の声）
見らんね 風間　わしが勝つばい
I'm going to win.
This man you're so crazy about...
貴様(きさん)がほれちょる こん男に
わしが！
I'll beat him!
勝つばい！
（スマイル）シューッ
Out!
（主審）アウト！
ツーナイン　月本選手
Two-nine, Tsukimoto!
Th-This kid...
（真田の声）こ… こいつ…
Damn.
He figured it out.
（卓の声）バレたか
ポケットに球を集中されると
真田はもろい
Sanada can't handle a string of attacks to his middle.
He's brutal and merciless.
（オババ）冷酷無慈悲だ
分かるか？ 道夫
Can you tell, Michio?
That's the power of the Smile monster.
そいつが
スマイルモンスターの力だよ
（真田の声）
今まで試しよったとか？
わしんこと
He was testing me this whole time?
球 散らせて打ちよったんは
そんためか！
Is that why he was spraying shots far and wide?
You little brat!
こんガキ！
海王 ナメちょったら
ぼてくりこかすぞ！
When you take Kaiou lightly, we take you down hard!
いきます
Here I come.
（真田の声）チクショー！
Shit!
I can keep slammin' them,
たたけど たたけど—
こげん正確に拾われとっては
一向に らちが…
but if he keeps makin' such precise returns, I won't... get anywhere!
ネット
Net!
Eleven-nine! Game goes to Tsukimoto!
イレブンナイン
ゲーム トゥ 月本選手
ダアッ…
What a guy.
何ちゅう野郎だ
ひっくり返しちまったぜ おい
He actually turned it around.
He took ten points in a row off Sanada.
（男性）10点連取だよ 真田から
Seriously? Is Sanada gonna lose
in the third round of the prelims?
（男性）マジかよ
真田が予選の３回戦で負けんの？
Way to go!
（小泉(こいずみ)）ウェイ トゥ ゴー！
What's going on?
（真田の声）どうなっちょる
まるで隙が見えん
I can't see any openings.
どこ打ちよってん崩れよらん
No matter where I hit it, he doesn't falter.
On top of that, this guy...
おまけに こいつ…
He's a real tough guy.
ホント タフだぜ
（主審）アウト！
Out!
Eleven-two! Game goes to Tsukimoto!
イレブンツー
ゲーム トゥ 月本選手
ハァ… ハァ…
I gotta hand it to him.
（真田の声）
恐れ入ったわ　どうにもならん
I couldn't do a thing.
He really is strong.
ほんに強かばい
It's no wonder Kazama wants him.
風間が欲しがるわけじゃ
夢 見たばい
I was dreamin'.
ほんに貴様(きさん)は
太か男ばいのう 風間
You're a big man, Kazama.
Puttin' table tennis and the team first...
卓球 チームのことば
一番に考えちょった
Compared to you, I'm naïve and petty.
それん比べて わしゃ甘か
小さかばい
生半可(なまはんか)な気持ちじゃ
貴様(きさん)には太刀打ちできん
With this halfhearted attitude,
I could never compete with you.
I get why Yurie fell for you.
百合枝(ゆりえ)さんが貴様(きさん)にホレんのも
分かろうたい
（真田の声）
じゃが わしも海王の真田やけん
But I'm still Sanada of Kaiou!
You'd better collect my ashes, Kazama!
骨は拾ってもらうけんのう 風間！
えい
Get a move on, Muuko, or I'll leave you behind!
（アクマ）
ちんたらしてんじゃねえよ
ムー子(こ)！
置いてくぞ コラァ
Hey, Ma.
（ムー子）ねえ ねえ マー君
あっちで水泳がやってるってえ
It looks like there's swimming over there. Come on!
（ムー子）ねえ
（アクマ）ちっ
Go swim with them, then.
一緒に泳いでくりゃいいぜ
I'm going in.
俺 先 行ってんよ
Sheesh, I was only saying!
（ムー子）
何よお　言っただけじゃんよー
Come on!
ねえ 怒ったのぉ？
Are you mad?
ねえ マー君
Ma, come on, I'm talking to you!
Kong Wenge
Hoshino Yutaka
I could cry...
泣けるぜ
どこ行くの？ マー君
Where are you going, Ma?
試合 こっちだよ
They're playing over this way.
Toilet!
便所
ご無沙汰しています 風間さん
It's been a while, Kazama.
佐久間(さくま)です
It's Sakuma.
Sakuma Manabu.
佐久間 学(まなぶ)です
（ドラゴン）おう
Hey.
（アクマ）
半年ぶりになりますかね
It's been about six months since we last spoke, I think.
こうして
風間さんと お話しするの
Yeah.
元気にしていたか？
佐久間
How have you been, Sakuma?
何だよ
What?
元気でしたよ
I've been fine.
Good.
Sanada faces Tsukimoto in the third round, doesn't he?
真田さん ３回戦で
月本とぶつかってましたね
ああ 真田も
一流に違いないが—
Yeah.
There's no doubt that Sanada's a top player, but it'll be difficult for him to take even one game off that guy.
１ゲーム取ることすら困難だろう
真田さん 月本だけには
負けたくないでしょうね
I'm sure Tsukimoto is the last person Sanada would want to lose to.
勝利を望むのであれば—
If you want to win, you need to put in the effort.
それを成し遂げるための
努力が必要だ
You would say that.
風間さんに言わせれば
そうなのでしょうが
誰に言わせても同じだよ
Anyone would tell you the same thing.
Now that I've washed my hands of table tennis...
風間さんが こうして試合前
便所に立てこもる理由
I think I can finally get why you hole up in the can before your games.
卓球から足洗った今
ようやく分かる感じです
笑うか？
Going to laugh at me?
（アクマ）風間さん
誰のために卓球やってます？
Who do you play table tennis for?
Myself, of course.
無論 自分のため
Don't be ridiculous.
（アクマ）
冗談 言わないでください
If that were true, I wouldn't have...
今のが本音なら 俺だって何も…
ちっ
余計なこと言ってんな どうも
No, it's not my place to say this stuff.
Sorry, forget I said that.
すいません 忘れてください
行きます 俺
I'll leave now.
（ドラゴン）佐久間よ
Sakuma.
Do you resent me?
恨むか？ 私を
同情してますよ あなたには
I have only sympathy for you.
Not that you'd understand...
分からないでしょうけど
３連覇 期待してます
あなたならできる
I look forward to your three-peat.
I know you can do it.
Right.
Ma, do you have an upset stomach?
（ムー子）マー君 おなか痛いの？
（アクマ）なんでよ？
Why would you ask?
You took forever in there!
（ムー子）
全然 出てこないからあ
そこいろ ムー子　すぐ戻る
Stay there. I'll be right back.
What's with you, sheesh?
うーん 何よ それえ
少し泣く
I'm gonna go cry a bit.
I'm Gonna Go
Cry A Bit
ハア…
Hey.
（ドラゴン）よう
Hey, Kazama.
（猫田(ねこた)）
おう 風間　真田のやつがな…
Sanada...
Yeah.
It was like a nightmare.
まるで悪夢ば見とるごとあった
He's not human.
ありゃ 人間ではなか
わしには倒せん
I can't beat him.
Sakuma's here.
佐久間が来ているよ
Did you meet him?
会(お)うたのか？
Yeah. We talked a little.
うん 少し話をした
What'd he say?
あいつ 何ぞ言っとったか？
He said, "Who do you play table tennis for?"
“あなたは誰のために打つのか”と
ほいで 何ち？
What'd you say?
"For the team, of course."
無論 チームのためだと
ハッ 貴様(きさん)らしか答えじゃ
Sounds like you.
Wow!
（観客）すご！
Match goes to Kazama!
（主審）マッチ トゥ 風間選手
っしゃー！ シャラッ！
Yeah!
Oh yeah!
Kaiou Academy
Kazama Ryuuichi
Advances to
the Semifinals
Kaiou Academy
Kazama Ryuuichi
Advances to
the Semifinals
(Kaiou Academy)
Kazama Ryuuichi
（選手）痛っ…
（猫田）っしゃー！
Yeah!
（主審）マッチ トゥ 猫田選手
Match goes to Nekota!
Kaiou Academy
Nekota Shuuji
Advances to
the Semifinals
Kaiou Academy
Nekota Shuuji
Advances to
the Semifinals
(Kaiou Academy)
Kazama Ryuuichi
Nekota Shuuji
(Kaiou Academy)
Katase High School
Tsukimoto Makoto
Advances to
the Semifinals
Katase High School
Tsukimoto Makoto
Advances to
the Semifinals
(Kaiou Academy)
Kazama Ryuuichi
Nekota Shuuji
(Kaiou Academy)
Tsukimoto Makoto
(Katase High School)
Nine-ten, Okano!
（主審）ナインテン　岡野(おかの)選手
Yeah!
（岡野）シャラッ！
ハァ ハァ ハァ…
Your shots are all over the place, Peco!
球が浮っついてんだよ
ペコ 球が！
あと１本だろ １本！
You only need one more point! One!
He doesn't drag things out for the fun of it, Michio.
あの子だって 好きこのんで
もたついてやしないよ 道夫
万全なら この程度の連戦で—
If everything were right with him, a few matches in a row wouldn't tire him out.
あご上げて打ちやしねえよ
He's blown his knee out.
膝 いかれてんな ありゃ
Yeah.
He's off-balance because he's favoring it.
それを かばうから
上下のバランスを失う
オーバートレーニングの
代償ってやつだ
That's the cost of over-training.
Out!
（主審）アウト！
マッチ トゥ 星野選手
Match goes to Hoshino!
（歓声）
（ペコ）ハァ ハァ ハァ…
Peco...
ペコ…
It'll be dangerous for him to keep playing.
残りの試合は棄権だな
ハァ ハァ…
Katase High School Hoshino Yutaka
Advances to the Semifinals
(Kaiou Academy)
Kazama Ryuuichi
Nekota Shuuji
(Kaiou Academy)
Tsukimoto Makoto
(Katase High School)
Hoshino Yutaka
Tsukimoto              Nekota
Net!
（主審）ネット！
（猫田）ちっ！
（主審）テン ツー　月本選手
Ten-two, Tsukimoto!
（猫田の声）
はぁ… みじんのミスもない
He doesn't make even the tiniest mistake. The mistakes are always mine.
ミスすんのは常に こっちや
常に冷静　まったく疲れへん
He never loses his cool, never gets tired.
計算し尽くされ 正確無比の技術
He's got perfectly calculated, flawless technique...
サーブして よろしいでしょうか
May I serve now?
He's just like a robot.
（猫田の声）
まさにロボットや　ハッ
ええで
Sure.
（猫田の声）こいつ 血一滴も
通っとらんのちゃうか？
Is there even blood running through his veins?!
（主審）マッチ トゥ 月本選手
Match goes to Tsukimoto!
（歓声）
（猫田）泣きたなるわ
It makes me want to cry.
(Kaiou Academy)
Nekota Shuuji
Tsukimoto Makoto
(Katase High School)
(Kaiou Academy)
Kazama Ryuuichi
Hoshino Yutaka
(Katase High School)
Tsukimoto Makoto
Great work, Tsukimoto!
よくやった 月本！
（高村）ナイスファイッ！
（スマイル）どうも
Nice fight!
Thanks.
You were amazing! I was seriously impressed!
（大田）
すげえぜ　マジで感激したよ
（スマイル）星野は？
（高村）まだだ
What about Hoshino?
He hasn't played yet.
The doc says his knee is in real bad shape.
あいつの膝 マジ悪(わり)いってな
Is it?
（スマイル）そうですか
（大田）おう
Yeah.
What's your problem?!
（高村）何だ おい！
応援しねえの？ 星野の試合！
You're not gonna cheer for Hoshino?
おい 君！ どうなってる
こっちの対戦相手は！
Hey, you! What's going on?
Where's our opponent?
アップ済ませた選手の体が
冷えるだろ！
Our player's warmed up,
and now his muscles will get cold!
いつまで待たせる！
How long do we have to wait?
I'm sorry! I'll get him now!
すみません 今すぐ はい！
What now? Do you want to practice a little?
どうする？ 少し打ってるか？
いえ 平気です
No, I'm fine.
I guess so.
そうだな
This match is going to get called off.
流れるな この試合
（ペコ）平気だよ 道夫さん
痛み止め打ったし
I'm fine, Michio.
They shot me up with painkillers.
You don't know how much trouble knee injuries can be!
お前は膝の怖さを知らん！
You made it to the semis, so you can quit now and still play at nationals!
ベスト４ 残ったから—
ここでやめても
全国大会があんだろう！
I'll play.
（ペコ）やる
（道夫）おい！
Hey!
Er, Kaiou is saying...
（スタッフ）あの 海王さんが…
It's too dangerous!
棄権だ 棄権！
今 行く
Be right there.
Um...
あの…
ちっと待っとけ 坊主
You just wait a second, kid.
Huh?
Listen to me, Peco.
いいかい？ ペコ
Players your age need to be rash and reckless sometimes.
確かに お前さんぐらいの年にゃ
無茶だの無謀は必要だ
But if you want to be world champ,
ただ お前が この世界で
てっぺん目指すなら—
白旗あげる勇気ってのも
覚えないとね
you also need the courage to raise the white flag.
I've been playing since I still had Mongolian spots.
これでも ケツに
蒙古斑(もうこはん)つけてるころから—
打ってんだ
I've seen lots of guys before me cry after wrecking their knees.
膝 壊して 泣いた先輩
たくさん見てきた
And I know you quit because you wrecked yours, old lady.
オババが膝 壊して卓球やめたんも
知ってるんさ
Then why?!
だったら！
スマイルが呼んでんよ
Smile's calling me.
He never smiled, so people gave him stupid nicknames like "Robot" or "Golgo."
あいつ 笑わないんで—
Walking
Robot
ロボットだのゴルゴだの
とんちきな あだ名 付けられて—
Walking
Robot
Automatic
Vacuum
すげえ いじめられててさ
He got picked on a ton.
いつも１人で—
He always just sat by himself and played games his dad bought him.
親父(おやじ)から買ってもらったっていう
ゲームばっかやってやがった
But when I taught him to play table tennis, he smiled a ton.
けど卓球 教えてやったら
えれえ笑ったんよ
僕もペコみたいになれるかな？
Think I can be like you, Peco?
僕 ペコみたいになりたいんだ
I want to be like you.
ペコみたいに
Like you!
（ペコ）
けど タムラで写真見るまで
すっかり忘れてた
But I'd totally forgotten until I saw that photo at Tamura.
It's not that he's "Smile" because he doesn't smile—
笑わないから
スマイルじゃなくて—
I called him that because he smiled when he played table tennis.
卓球やってる時 笑ってたから
スマイルって呼んだんだ
Call me when you're in a pinch!
（子供のペコ）
ピンチの時には おいらを呼びな
そうすりゃ
おいらが やってくる！
If you do that, I'll come to you!
He's been waiting for me for a real long time now.
（ペコ）あいつは もう
ずっと長いこと俺を待っている
ずっと長いこと俺を信じている
He's believed in me for a real long time.
The reason he stopped smiling is because my playing got lame.
あいつが笑わんくなったんは—
おいらの卓球が
しょっぱくなってたから
I knew, but I pretended not to notice.
気がついてたけど
知らんふりしてた
I was scared, so I plugged my ears for all I was worth.
ビビって必死に耳ふさいでたさ
But it's time for me to go to him.
でも そろそろ行ってやんねえと
Michio, gimme my racket.
道夫さん
ラケットくれろ
Before I do that, I gotta take
down one more giant monster!
その前に—
もう１匹 でけえ怪獣
退治しなきゃよ！
Peco. Are you playing for Smile?
（オババ）ペコ
スマイルのために打つのかい？
違(ちげ)えよ オババ
No way!
I'm doing it 'cause I'm the hero, duh!
おいらが
ヒーローだからっしょ！
And don't you forget it!
そこんとこ よろしく！
I love ya, Peco.
愛してるぜ ペコ
（子供のペコ）
心の中で３回 唱えろ！
Chant this three times in your mind!
ヒーロー見参 ヒーロー見参
Enter the hero!
ヒーロー見参！
If you do that, I'll come to you!
そうすりゃ
おいらが やってくる！
（スタッフ）
ちょっと通してください
選手が出ます！
Let us through!
Player coming through!
I'll come from Planet Ping Pong!
（子供のペコ）
ピンポン星から やってくる！
Yeah!
っしゃー！
Semifinal Match
Kazama
vs
Hoshino
A red sun stares at me
The world goes blurry when I yawn
My wishes fluctuate like a metronome
Everything tells me this is the end
I do have some dreams, you know
Sometimes we breathe
and just seem to inhale the smoke of someone
somewhere out of sight
Then we are pure determination
I don't understand this wonderland
I won't get wet even if it rains
This is a wonderland
Once I've made it through this long tunnel
I'm sure that someone will kiss me